seedurl.com 2017-02-18

# Seedurl.com Absolutely Free File Hosting and Sharing Service for you! Free File Upload

**General**  
Seedurl.com respects your concerns about maintaining the privacy of your data that is submitted to us through your use of the Seedurl.com web site. This Privacy Policy only applies to the Seedurl.com web site and does not apply to data collected on any other web site, including other web sites to which this site may be link. Seedurl.com maintains separate web sites for some of its subsidiaries...

**Aggregated Information**  
Through this web site, Seedurl.com collects and stores non-personal information in aggregate form. The data are collected and stored for internal statistical purposes.

Seedurl.com also collects and stores individual data to maintain and issue a unique session ID for individuals while they are at this site.

Non-personal information includes:

\- the browser type with which you access the Internet;  
\- the date and time you accessed the Seedurl.com website;  
\- the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to Seedurl.com  
\- information you viewed while visiting our site.

**Personal Information Collected on this Site**  
Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not use or otherwise disclose any of the personal data that you provide.

**How Seedurl.com Collects Your Information**  
In specific instances, Seedurl.com processes personally identifiable information that you submit via this web site. Personal information is submitted via this web site through New Account submission, Job submission (by online form or online resume), or through an e-mail sent to this site.

You may choose not to submit personal information via New Account submission, Job submission, or e-mail via this web site. By sending personal information to Seedurl.com, via this web site, you acknowledge that Seedurl.com will process certain personally identifiable data about you. You therefore consent to our use of that information in accordance with the Seedurl.com Worldwide Privacy Policy.

**How Seedurl.com Uses Your Information**  
We will never sell or provide personal data to a third party, except as provided in this Privacy Policy, without your express consent. We may process your personal data that we receive through a submission from you to Seedurl.com, via this web site.

We may use your personal data in aggregate form for internal statistical purposes, for the direct marketing of Seedurl.com events, or for employment purposes, by way of employment form or resume submission. The information collected on the Seedurl.com website via New Account submission and/or Job submission form is the only information used for the direct marketing of other Seedurl.com events. If you do not wish to be contacted for further Seedurl.com events, you must check the opt-out box on the registration form.

We may disclose personal data in response to a court order or other legal obligation. In the highly unlikely event that a liquidator, administrator or receiver is appointed over Seedurl.com or all or any part of our assets, we may transfer your information to a third-party purchaser of the business if that purchaser undertakes to only use your personal data as set out in this Privacy Policy.

**Accuracy:**

Seedurl.com does not vouch for, and is not responsible for, the accuracy of data about you that may be supplied to us through your email or through any other submission of personal information through this web site.

**Security:**

Seedurl.com will take all appropriate measures to assure the online security of transmissions to this web site. Seedurl.com web site and any data transmitted to or from it are protected by a secure socket layer (SSL) key, which encrypts the data. All data is stored on our servers in a secure, encrypted manner. Access to those servers is strictly limited to network administrators and other authorized personnel of Seedurl.com, who have been trained to protect against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of personal data under Seedurl.com control. We take pride in our technology and our security policies.

Seedurl.com reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know how we will use the information that is collected about you.
